<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Hey!,I am Hari</title>
    <link>https://picklehari.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Hey!,I am Hari</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 12:21:57 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://picklehari.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Big data: Tool for empowering people</title>
      <link>https://picklehari.github.io/posts/big-data-and-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 10:06:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://picklehari.github.io/posts/big-data-and-people/</guid>
      <description>Living in a data prosperous society, I wonder if the data revolution is the 21st-century renaissance. Big data could be considered analogous to the printing press of the early 15th century. Organisations such as Datakind, has made crash models for streets in New York and New Orleans helping governments redesign roads and prevent accidents. Open maps have made University students in Tandale (A district in Tanzania) to mark key local resources and services and thus in turn help organizations serve the citizens better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the social multiverse</title>
      <link>https://picklehari.github.io/posts/exploring-the-social-multiverse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 10:06:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://picklehari.github.io/posts/exploring-the-social-multiverse/</guid>
      <description>Over the past 20 years of my existence, I have tended to realize over and over that there tends to be another undiscovered social universe beyond what we live in, and the key to visit and unlock these mystery universes is to interact with other beings, human or nonhuman. The popular science communicator Bill Nye said: “Every person you meet, knows something you don’t”. I believe this philosophy can be applied to far beyond human beings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I believe Cutting edge isn&#39;t always revolutionising</title>
      <link>https://picklehari.github.io/posts/why-big-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 10:06:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://picklehari.github.io/posts/why-big-data/</guid>
      <description>Being born in a time when Internet and computer technology was miracles in the eyes of the common folk and at a very rural area ,I have seen how this &amp;ldquo;magic&amp;rdquo; have rapidly changed lives and perceptions of even the poorer sections of society. Growing up admist all the middle class family drama I was exposed to the wonders of Internet and computers from my very childhood that I almost took it for granted.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>